Copies
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Copies, 2.1.1.1.32
  - Josef Poniatowski, copy, Helena Modrywike, copy, Jan Kilinski, copy, and Stanislaw Staszic, copy [split negative], before 1914; 6; 0988; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1260)
  - Mickiewicza monument, copies for Poland lecture [split negative], before 1914; 7; 0989; 8x10 (Box 1260)
  - Wawel od ul. Grodzkiej, copies for Poland lecture [split negative], before 1914; 8; 0990; 8x10 (Box 1260)
  - Wawel Cathedral, copy, and Church of Mother of God the Queen, copies for Poland lecture [split negative], before 1914; 9; 0991; 8x10 (Box 1260)
  - Wawel Royal Castle, copy, ornate building, copy, Wawel Royal Castle, distant view, copy, and Friends of Fine Arts Academy, copy, for Poland lecture [split negative], before 1914; 10; 0992; 8x10 (Box 1260)
  - Street scene, copy, ornate building, copy, Cloth Hall, copy, and Kosciuszki Mound, copy, Poland [split negative], before 1914; 11; 0993; 8x10 (Box 1260)
  - Carved archway, Orequipa[?], copy, 1908 December 31; 12; 0994; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1260)
  - Victoria Theater, Valparaiso Chile, copy, 1908 December 31; 13; 0995; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1260)
  - Theater, Santiago Chile, copy, 1908 December 31; 14; 0996; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1260)
  - Building with many windows, Santiago Chile, copy, 1908 December 31; 15; 0997; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1260)
  - Military school, Santiago Chile, copy, 1908 December 31; 16; 0998; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1260)
  - Corner of large building, Santiago Chile, copy, 1908 December 31; 17; 0999; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1260)
  - Street scene, La Paz Bolivia, copy, 1908 December 31; 18; 1000; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1260)
  - Stairs, La Paz Bolivia, copy, 1908 December 31; 19; 1001; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1260)
  - Spanish hospital, Montevideo Uruguay, copy, 1908 December 31; 20; 1002; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1260)
  - Train station, Montevideo Uruguay, copy, 1908 December 31; 21; 1003; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1260)
  - Pan-American Congress building in Rio where first congress was held, Brazil, copy, 1908 December 31; 22; 1004; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1260)
  - Palace of Emperors, Brazil, copy, 1908 December 31; 23; 1005; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1260)
  - Queen of Sweden, copy, Crown Prince Gustav Adolf, copy, Crown Princess Margareta with Prince Bertil, copy, and Gustav V, copy [split negative], 1915 January 8; 24; 1006; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1260)
  - Chief Atchee, chief on reservation, Eastern Utah, copy, before 1916; 25; 1007; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1260)
  - Globe, showing Europe, copy [broken], 1909; 26; 1008; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1260)
  - Picture writing, Yellow Jacket Canyon Colorado, copy, rock bridge, copy, North End Cliff Palace, Mesa Verde National Park, copy, and round tower, Ruin Canyon Utah, copy [split negative], before 1915; 27; 1009; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1260)
  - Four adobe buildings, copies [split negative], before 1915; 28; 1010; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1260)
  - Adobe building, copy, two people looking over edge, copy, pottery, copy and mummies, copy [split negative], before 1915; 29; 1011; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1260)
  Box 1261
- Copies, 2.1.1.1.32
  - Cottage, copy, and sheep in field, copy [split negative], 1912 December; 1; 1012; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1261)
  - Man and woman on donkeys, and river scene [split negative], before 1916; 2; 1013; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1261)
  - Cottage, copy, buildings, copy and street scene, copy [split negative], before 1916; 3; 1014; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1261)
  - Little girl outside tent, copy, 1908 April 16; 4; 1015; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1261)
  - Rock formations, copy, rock with wagons in front, copy, man in front of rock formation, copy [split negative], 1913; 5; 1016; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1261)
  - Lifting a horse, copy, Major J. McLaren, copy, Major A. E. Kimmins, copy, Lieutenant W.D.P. Jarvis, copy, Captain G.J.L. Smith, copy, Madame Joffre, copy, diagrams, copy and map, copy [split negative], before 1916; 6; 1017; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1261)
  - Lieutenant R.G. Crawford, copy, and man at table, copy [split negative], before 1916; 7; 1018; 5x7 (Box 1261)
  - Church in distance, copy, and country scene, copy [split negative], before 1916; 8; 1019; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1261)